EZEIFEJAFOR Dominic

Frontend developer

I am a highly motivated professional and dedicated front-end developer with 2 years experience in developing and integrating pixel-perfect designs and maintaining frontend web applications. Adept at problem-solving and using the adequate technologies to bring designs to life so as to proffer solutions and ensure customer satisfaction. I'm eager to embrace new ideas and learn new skills. I'm always ready to bring my strong interpersonal skills to whatever team I may find myself.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Gruve Ticketing, Lagos — *Intern*

September 2022 - October 2023

While interning at Gruve ticketing, I was committed to learning to the best of my abilities as well as interacting with real life projects.

Sippy, Lagos — Front-end dev

November 2023 - Present

At Sippy, I was responsible for the implementation of designs within a full-stack Next.js e-commerce solution, transforming client ideas into highly functional, responsive, and high-performance user interfaces, including critical features such as user authentication, secure payment integration, and an intuitive admin dashboard, all aimed at enhancing the overall E-commerce experience.

EDUCATION:

UNIVERSITY OF BENIN, Benin City, Edo — B.Eng, Petroleum Engineering

January 2014 - December 2019

Bachelor's of Petroleum Engineering

CONTACT

Address: : 12, mike and mike
Avenue, Peace Estate, Ipaye, Iba,

Ojo, Lagos

Phone no: 08101837449

Mail: dominicezeifejafor@gmail.com

SKILLS:

HTML CSS

SASS Javascript

Typescript React

NextJS Chakra UI

Tailwind CSS Git

Redux